[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]
[heavy music]
[Referee/English] Next shooting match
[English] Preparation
[English] Start
[English] Preparation and Aiming Time
It's 5 minutes
[English] Start
[English] 30 seconds ago
[Tang]
[English] Preparation
[English] Start
[Tang]
“Load, start, don’t stop!”
[Wham - Siren]
I'll go out for a moment and come back
I brought some Yun Dong-ju clothes too.
Do you need anything?
senior
[Calm music]
I really like Dongju a lot
I'm sorry, senior.
Don't say you're sorry
It feels like I really lost
I'll go and come back
[Mansik] Hey, what the hell?
How is it going?
What about the Commissioner?
[Daeyong] There was a seminar suddenly yesterday.
I went to Seoul
I haven't been able to contact you since then.
- What about Minjooyoung?
- I'm looking for it.
It's difficult to track where they're hiding.
I couldn't even see the head of the police department.
I can't even contact you
You went on a business trip to the US a few days ago.
It seems like you've been here for quite some time.
There's no one to help me
But is Yoon Dong-ju okay?
Where are you now?
I moved it to a safe place first.
It's not that good
[Detective] Team leader
[Nervous music]
[Wing - Cell Phone]
Yes, team leader
Team leader!
[Mansik] Oh
[Mansik sighs]
Oh my, it's a total asari version, huh?
The jurisdictional area is like this.
The commissioner’s bastard
Take it out, Mr.
I guess it goes according to Min-young Min’s plan.
- [Beep beep - radio]
- [click click]
[Drurr - Break]
[squeak]
[click - car door]
[Rattle rattle]
How are you? uh? Haha
Ugh, Mr.
- Where are you going?
- [Bangbang!]
[Sanggon's scream]
[Noisy]
[Seokchun] Ugh!
*cub
I can't hold back my mouth
Ah!
Hey, your tongue is the problem.
[Mansik] That damn bastard
I can't do anything because of one thing
Man, the police are so funny, huh?
Ugh, really! Mr.
[Daeyong] To this extent
If you see me leaving
Looks like the rumor is true
- [Interesting Music]
- [People laughing]
[Panel] Oh my, are you here, oh my.
[Chief Prosecutor] I am the head of the Supreme Prosecutor’s Office’s Criminal Division.
[Jonghyun]
I just met the detective chief.
The golden rabbit is due tomorrow
They say they will be transferred to the Seoul Supreme Prosecutors' Office.
- Please sit down.
- [Chief of Detectives] Ah, yes.
[Daeyong] The chief is like a great sword
There's a rumor that they're forming a new special team.
[Call connection tone]
[Jonghyun sighs]
[Wing - Cell Phone]
[People laughing]
- [Voice guidance] You can answer the phone...
- I don't accept it.
What the hell are you guys
What kind of trick are you playing! Mr.
[Jonghyun sighs]
They're trying to cover everything up.
Just in case, first of all
From materials secured at pawnshops
Let’s move it quickly.
Why is it like this again? uh?
Hey, wake up! hey!
[Jonghyun] Hey there
He's already dead
- [Call connection tone]
- pawn shop
Pick up the phone, pawn shop!
- Stay in the back, man.
- [Call end sound]
Did I come into the wrong office again?
uh? What happened?
[Mansik] No
What happened to this!
[Pawnshop owner] Wow, huh
great eagle, bald eagle
- Gwangse?
- [Pawnshop owner] Gwangse!
- Look for a bright place.
- [Mansik] Gwangse, Gwangse!
[Pawnshop owner]
Find the shining one!
- Gwangse!
- [Jonghyun] Wait a minute
- [Thump thump]
- [Nervous music]
[Boom boom!]
- came
- [Sergei] Oh
Food is here, go out, go out
Go out and get some food
- ♪ On a rainy day ♪
- [Jingle jingle]
♪ Eat Jjambbong ♪
- [Leo] Hey
- Oh!
- [Bang!]
- [Sergei’s moans]
[Leo's laughter]
[Leo/Russian] Hello
[Muttering]
hey
[Sergei groans]
[Russian] Who are you?
[Russian] Where are those bastards?
- [Bang!]
- [Sergei’s scream]
Why are you here now?
[Mansik] Hey, you
I'm sick, don't I have to go to the hospital?
[Gwangse] Ah...
After going to the hospital
If you get caught by those guys for no reason
This time, I won't even be able to find a bone and die.
[sigh]
Sergeant Kim, contact the police.
[Pawnshop Owner] Dazzling Head
That's why the bullet missed
I don't think I'll die
- I was lucky.
- [Jonghyun] Yes, this is Sergeant Kim Jonghyun.
This is Inseong Pawnshop.
Please request support
- [Meaningful music]
- [Call end sound]
[Pawn shop owner] I don’t think I’ll die.
I won't die, nigga
I'll live until all my hair falls out
[Jonghyun] Team leader
- It's a little strange.
- [Mansik] What?
simply from scratch
If the intention was to kill
To this extent
I don't think I did it
That's right
just at once
I didn't mean to kill you.
Have you seen anything else?
[Gwangse/crying] That...
Three, Sergei
[Pawnshop owner] Yeah, yeah
Blah, blah...
Leo Vladimirovich Svarsky
[Small] Svar, Svarsky
[Sergei] Vladimir
Ilyich Svarsky
Wait a minute
Leo Vladimirovich Svarsky?
Those Russian people
his father's name
Said it was written in the name
If so
Rich or not
Saying that and stopping the shooting of anger
Just here and there...
[Tang]
[Sergei speaks in Russian]
[Russian] What?
that
why
Tell me now!
[Loud gunshot]
Then Sergei
I threw something at you
[Pawn shop owner] You bastards
don't be scared
[Gwangse’s cry]
Hey, I'm so scared out there.
I have a chronic illness, heart disease.
Please get out of here
No tenge for office use
Please leave now
You are the best evil in my life
Isn’t this the file from when you folded it?
[Jonghyun] Meanwhile, Hanna was alone
I think they were investigating.
To this extent, Inspector Ji
You were investigating?
[Russian] Did you find her?
[Man/Russian] I went by car
I'm sure, but I don't know where it went.
[Russian] She can't contact me
[Russian] Find it, right now
[Wing - Cell Phone]
Hey, President Min
[Jooyoung] How did it go?
Oh, I packed all my stuff.
The car hasn't arrived yet
I can't pay for that meal
A cub like a raccoon
Have a procrastination, Mr.
upon arrival
Move things on time
[Seokchun] But if you find out that something is gone
Can you stay still?
I'm going to be a little busy today
I have some business to run.
[Seokchun] How did you tell me that?
Because the deal is over
I have to keep my promise
What about Yoon Dong-ju?
[Seokchun] I’m looking for the mutt.
downtown Inseong
Because I'm searching like crazy
It'll be out soon
But what if you find it?
Catch me alive?
What are you doing, bothering me?
just
Kill it, cleanly.
[dark music]
[Jooyoung] Count down
If you hit round 12
- [Eerie sound effect]
- Did you think it would all end?
It was fun so far
die well and feel good
[Sigh!]
[Hannah] Yoon Dong-ju
Come to your senses
Yoon Dong-ju, look at me.
Dongjuya
It's okay, it's okay, Dongju.
uh
[Calm music]
Never again
I thought you couldn't see me
Because I can see it like this
good
Chi...
don't laugh
I feel stupid
you
I want to see more of your face
Joe, I'm sleepy
It's because of the energy
sleep more
내가 옆에 있을게
[Woman/trembling] Who, who are you?
sister
[Dreamy music]
[마귀 언니] 어?
uh?
찾았다, 내 핀
thank you
But
Who are you?
If you sent me like that
넌 잘 살아야지
왜 이렇게 살아?
Throw me in that trash can
온다며
You said you would follow me too
Do you know how I lived?
at least you
At least you don't forget me
I came here because I wanted to kill you.
What if you don’t know me?
Look, who am I?
No matter how much I change
You said my eyes remember
Look
Look straight!
[Demon Sister] Hehehe...
Please give me some more candy
If you just stay here quietly
You said you would give me candy.
Give it to me now, candy!
eww! Ugh...
[Devil] Who did that?
that said
Who did it?
[Anchor/Radio] All over Inseong City
riotous
Went out with gangsters...
[Anchor/TV] They are currently
wanted
He said he would catch police officer Yoon Dong-ju himself.
For causing such an uproar
It turns out
The same incident is still happening
It keeps happening...
[Buzz - Cell Phone]
[Oh Eun-ah’s ‘Thousand stars’]
[Wing - Cell Phone]
Yes, constable
[Police officer Oh] It’s none other than
In the past, when Inspector Ji Hanna found a gun,
You asked me to contact you.
[Police officer Oh] Oh my, today too
I guess you're going to the airport to help out.
I just need to give you one gun, right?
[Hannah] No, please give me everything.
All my guns and ammo
All that ammunition?
yes
Because a harmful assistant is wandering around
I'm trying to catch it
[Police Officer Oh/Phone] It was shipped today
Because you took it.
- [Call connection tone]
- [Mansik] Now, open it.
[Pawnshop owner] Oh, really.
- [Mansik] Pull
- [Pawnshop Owner] Ayu
[Voice guidance] Can't connect...
[Pawnshop owner]
I can't open it, really
Are your legs sore?
[Man-sik] Where did Inspector Ji go?
Ome, ome, omega
What is this, huh?
[Gwangse] Uh, Officer Yoon.
- [Pawnshop Owner] Oh my
- [Gwangse] Oh my...
[Pawnshop owner]
They say great fortune is coming
Only bad things happen
Ugh
[Pawnshop owner]
I'm going to harpoon that guy.
Why?
[Splendid music]
[Buzzing - heavy equipment]
[Organizer/Chinese] Hurry up!
[Seokchun] Do it quickly!
By any chance, is it Inspector Ji Hanna?
Would you have applied there?
Uh, haven't you heard anything?
Okay
[Call end sound]
[Jonghyun] Not at the airport
[Mansik] Kang Gyejangdo and Daeyongido
I don't think I know
Hannah is the most recent
What were you investigating?
[Meaningful music]
[Pawn shop owner] Ottala registration
What did you say while looking at it?
- [Jonghyun] ‘David Oh’?
- David Oh?
David Oh
Ottala's son's name is the same.
Ottala son?
Oh, I'm dying
I heard you immigrated to America.
That's right, huh?
He's a guy who likes girls.
My son's name is Talamaengki.
Build it globally
[Jonghyun] David Oga
This is Minjooyoung.
Hannah
I think I know where it went
[nervous music]
[sigh]
I go to the office and ask for support.
I'll go right away
If anything happens, contact me right away.
- Take care of yourself.
- [Jonghyun] Yes
[Mansik] And you
Don't go anywhere
I'm watching Dongju carefully here.
[Pawnshop owner] Okay.
- [Jonghyun] Please
- [Pawnshop owner] Yes.
Wait, ‘you guys’?
Why is that bastard giving me orders?
[Seokchun] Hey, President Min!
- [Bang!]
- [Approaching car engine sound]
[Seokchun] Hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey!
야, 이 머저리 같은 년, 저, 씨
[마귀] 하, 씨...
[쿵쿵쿵]
[조선족] 문 열어라, 문 열어
문 열어
미친 새끼
일로 와
언니 잘 만나고 왔어?
How are you feeling? It’s been a while since I last saw you?
So out of mind
I don't know if you recognized me
[Seokchun] Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Sit down, sit down!
Don't lose your strength
[The devil's rough breathing]
Why?
Taste what my brother made
I just gave it to you as a gift
What are you so sad about?
To American drug dealers
He's the one who sent you in his place
Weren't you going to kill me anyway?
Even if you kill me, I will kill you!
what are you
What are you, why!
'why'?
Are you asking because you don’t know that?
Don’t you think you’ve seen this somewhere?
[heavy music]
Just endure 10 minutes
no, bitch
Why are you acting so nice, huh?
Save people too
I don't even sell drugs to women.
Drug addicts don't do drugs
That's pretense
[Devil] Yes, I like you
Because it’s consistent
[Jooyoung] Have you stopped taking medication?
Has it been over 10 years?
[석춘] 이야
[Jooyoung] Eat this and forget everything
- [Seokchun] Hey, raise your head
- 'Ah'
Say ‘ah’, say ‘ah’
[The devil’s heavy groans]
[Seokchun] Yes, swallow it.
[Seokchun’s laughter]
[Jooyoung] Better than yours
It will be effective
I tweaked your recipe a little bit.
[Seokchun] Hey, hey, hey
How much does it cost?
뱉으면 어떡하니
- [Eerie sound effect]
- It's a waste.
[heavy music]
That's right
If you're a bad bitch
나쁜 년답게 살아야지, 이게
아이고, 이게 뭐야, 어?
[Wing - Cell Phone]
- [마귀의 옅은 웃음]
- [Jooyoung’s sigh]
Hello
[Seokchun] President Min
President Min, are you okay?
[dark music]
Hey, what kind of bastard!
what are you doing!
안에 있는 쥐새끼 잡아라!
[석춘] 민 사장, 괜찮소?
Let's go, let's go in.
[Bang!]
They are a group
어디 가는, 어디 가는 거야?
- [Wham - Siren]
- Hey, stop! Stop!
Stop for a moment!
야, 우리 좀 도와줘
우리 좀 도와달라고!
[Call connection tone]
Daeyong-ah
대용아, 우리 좀 도와줘
A group of kids
Where are you heading to?
It's Victory Hotel.
[Reporter] Yes, recently discovered
To reveal the source of the cash
Inseong Police Agency and Inseong District Prosecutors' Office
Together with the Supreme Prosecutors' Office
Joint special investigation headquarters of prosecutors and police
Announced to install
[Daeyong] Ah, Mr.
People who do shit here
It's all coming together now
[Mansik] What are the remaining troops in the Qing Dynasty?
[Daeyong] Even if there is, no one comes forward.
About that bastard now
Even if I just open my mouth
Thank you.
Even if it was leaked to the media, there was no response.
These things are going crazy, huh?
That bastard says they will survive
Suck my butt and sit down! Mr.
[Daeyong] Oh, that’s right, Inspector Ji.
I heard you stopped by in the morning.
my child
Well, it might be a little uncomfortable.
In order for us to maintain security
Yes, each person has a cell phone.
We will collect it.
There are a lot of reporters
Always be careful
- [clack - gun]
- [Organization member] It's over there, catch it!
[조직원들] 잡아, 씨!
[Splendid music]
[Groans of organization members]
[Bang!]
[Clap]
[The spirit of the organization members]
[Bang!]
[Tak]
[spirited]
President Min, are you okay?
Mr.
[Jooyoung] Ha, sir...
[Call connection tone]
[석춘] 어떻게 됐니?
Hey, you idiots
Can't you catch that one?
야, 지금 총이 문제야?
Get it now, Mr.
- [Dark Music]
- 민 사장, 먼저 올라가 있소
[Ding! - Elevator]
[Beep]
Where is Minjooyoung?
[조직원] 야, 이, 씨
Ah!
[Tang]
[clack - gun]
2, 20th floor
Or, me, pen, pent, penthouse
There, there...
[Beep]
[Intense music plays]
[Organization member] Oh, where are you? Mr.
Hey, look for it quickly.
[Organization members] Yes
[Organization member] It’s over there.
[Rough breathing]
[MAX's 'GET IN THE RING']
[Loud gunshot]
[Clap-clack-clack-gun]
- [Bang!]
- [Groans of organization members]
[Groans from organization members]
[Seokchun] Hey, it’s over there, kill it!
Hey, this dog...
Oh, kid!
what are you doing! Catch that bitch and kill her!
- eww!
- [Loud gunshot]
[Loud gunshot]
[Seokchun] Did you kill him?
[Tense music]
[Organization members chuckle]
- [Bang!]
- [Groans of organization members]
[Bang bang!]
- [Tang]
- Mr. [Seokchun]
This guy*
Are there all these crazy gannas!
[Organization Member 1] What!
- [Organization Member 2] Who is it?
- [Organization Member 1] What! Mr.
[Organization Member 3] Come to work, you bastard.
[The spirit of the organization members]
[Organization member 1] Come to work
[Organization Member 2] Ugh!
[Groaning from member 3]
[The spirit of the organization members]
[Clap]
[Ding! - Elevator]
[Nervous music]
[rattling]
Just something like this
Are you trying to kill me?
[Hannah] Ah!
[Jooyoung] Ah...
If I had hit it right, I would have died.
[Clap]
But our shooting fairy
I guess my skills have decreased a lot
Or
Can't you hit a moving target?
[click]
[Hannah] I guess so
So run away till the end
If you stop you die
[Jooyoung] Why is everyone
Are you anxious because you can’t kill me?
[Hannah] Because you are a bad person
Jinsu Lee, a customs official
fake murder in car accident
Kyung-il Lee
Forced to make false statements and instigated murder
to cover up the incident
prison guard murders teacher
Smuggling of cars and illegal weapons
Drug manufacturing, distribution, and sales
Bribery, obstruction of official duties
There
Attempted murder of a police officer has also been added.
Ha, if he's this bad
Can't I just kill him?
I don't remember
[Hannah’s heavy breathing]
Ah
I remembered
I switched to a binary car
Instigating murder
Manufacturing, distributing, and selling drugs
I did it
Is there any solid evidence?
no
If I have any proof
Did you think you could catch it?
No matter how much you bark
no one knows
who am i
what have i done
Now you know everything
what kind of guy are you
Who owns that money?
[Powerful music]
[Hannah] Please
Team leader, please only open the broadcast channel.
What kind of guy is that guy?
the world knows
[Hannah] Greetings, Minjooyoung.
Everyone will be watching in real time
[Team Leader] Huh...
[Detective 1]
Hey, shouldn’t I apply for the job?
[Detective 2] Hey, who came forward?
[Executive] Hey, Jaehong.
Hey, do you know what this is?
Is this a special teams thing? This
[Detective 1] Hey, is this a recording?
[Detective 2] No, it’s real time now.
[Detective 1] You’re crazy.
Wow, shoot this fucking cop?
Everyone is at Victory now, right?
This needs to be supported
Isn't it?
who is this? It looks ordinary
You're not even a criminal?
Isn’t this Inspector Ji Hanna?
Wow, he wanted to go out like that.
Isn't this too dangerous?
Team leader, have you seen this...
Team leader
Oh, what are you doing?
Hey, you guys upload it quickly too.
Do these people know this?
[Panel] Externally,
Through the Special Investigation Headquarters
By taking a strong response
playing the media
[Man] If it continues like this
We are also Inseong City
It's hard to cover anymore
[Panel] I know
So today
Through this place...
[Reporter] Lock the door from the inside
What on earth are you doing?
[noisy]
Hey, bring your phone.
[Deokgyu] Hey, hey, hey
Give me what's mine, what's mine, what's mine
Huh?
What's going on, this?
[Click - Moon]
[Gwangse] I want to buy udon ramen...
[Pawnshop owner] Shhh
[Gwangse] Oh, I’m surprised.
[Small] Why?
So what happened...
[Jooyoung] Ugh!
[dark music]
[Hannah moans]
Mr. [Seokchun]
Holy crap, Mr.
President Min
This is it
This is an average kid, huh?
Because of you, I threw away all my clothes, this
Had a very powdery feast, Lee, Mr.
Brother
[Seokchun] Ah, Mr. President Min
[sigh]
So does Yoon Dong-ju.
You guys are so annoying.
Please help me organize my things.
[Seokchun] Hey, you go down
Take care of the truck first.
[Korean-Chinese] Yes, I understand.
[Seokchun]
Hey, just stay still, okay?
let's go
[Pawnshop owner]
What are you doing? uh?
huh?
Ah, why do I take painkillers like this?
I have to go
[Pawn shop owner] Where are you going, huh?
Hey Dongju
Ah, Dongju
Where do I go with this body?
[Gwangse] Policeman Yoon, then you die!
[Pawnshop owner] Let’s go
A burden, a burden!
[Gwangse] Wow!
[Pawn shop owner, Gwangse’s scream]
- [Pawnshop owner] Constable Yoon
- [Gwangse] Wow!
Ugh...
Hey!
[Hannah] Uh, ah, ah...
[Rough breathing]
Ha, it's hard
Should we stop now?
It's the last way
Very impressive for both of them
I'll give you an experience
Ah, Mr.
[Hannah] Uh, uh...
[Jooyoung] Ugh!
[Bang!]
[intense music]
[Button operation sound]
[Elevator arrival sound]
[Korean-Chinese] What are you?
[wing]
[Mansik] Uh, what’s going on?
[Pawnshop owner]
We're not good enough, it's like madness
[Gwangse] Ugh! Save me, save me
[Pawn Shop Owner] Oh, yes, yes.
Catch him, catch him!
Stay still
Well done, good job
-Where are you going?
- [Gwangse] Constable Yoon! Constable Yoon!
[Mansik] What, what, what, what, what?
[Jaehong] Hey!
These kids
- Hey!
- [Somber Music]
[Organization members] Oh!
Ouch!
[Jaehong] Hey
Climb up, quickly!
dangerously
[Hannah] Ugh!
goodbye
[Bang!]
[Jalgrang - shell casing]
If you shoot that gun, you too will die.
[Calm music]
There are a lot of people targeting me today
But
Aren't you aiming the gun wrong?
No, it was this way from the beginning.
[Sergei/Russian] Your father
I know who killed it
[Russian] What?
[Russian] Who killed your father
People are not Otala
I know who killed your father
Shall I help you?
Who is that?
Ohtala
[Sergey/Russian]
the person who killed your father
[Russian] That gun
I'm the one who handed it to you
Hey, go
- [Bang!]
- [Sigh!]
- [Seokchun] Hey, Mr.
- [Leo’s groan]
The kitten is so excited
My back felt uncomfortable.
- [Leo] This bastard
- [Seokchun] Ugh!
[The devil's faint groan]
Ah! Mr.
President Min
Are you okay?
Ah, Mr.
I'm going down
- [Pawn Shop Owner] There is only one person left.
- Ugh.
- Ah, Mr.
- [Gwangse’s tears]
[Gwangse] Why did you come now, really?
[Pawnshop owner] Atta
It's been a while since I got punched
Shake shake shake
This is not a sound coming from your mouth
Shock, this is the sound of your feet
Ah, Dongju!
Dongju? Uh, I went to help out here.
Where!
[Roaring roar]
[Daeyong] Hey, hey
Get out of the way
[Daeyong] Hey, get out of the way
[nervous music]
[Roaring roar]
What is this, you bastard! Tsk
Bite your teeth tight, because your jaw is sticking out.
- [People’s surprised exclamations]
- [click click]
[Reporter] Take a picture quickly!
[Rhythmic music]
[Mansik] Are you okay?
What have you done?
Did you come here to die?
Bad guys need to be widely known
[Daeyong] Go quickly, quickly, quickly
[noisy]
Hurry up and go!
[Wham - Siren]
[Leo] Ah...
Why are you saving me?
Even now
Because I have to return the favor
[Man 1] Hey, where is your father going?
You came alone, huh?
[Men] Wow
- [Man 2] This guy
- [Hocheol] What is it, huh?
[Man 3] Well, you bastard.
[Man 3 moans]
[Man] Oh, you police bastard, run!
[Calm music]
Uh, it's okay
What's your name?
leo
How old are you?
eighteen years old
give it
This is for you
I don't think it suits me
[Leo] Maybe
god gave me
Maybe it's a chance for penance
wake up
[Devil's groan]
[Organization member] Hey!
[Jaehong] Ugh!
[The spirit of the organization members]
[Groans of organization members]
You weren't hurt much, right?
[The spirit of the organization members]
Hey!
[Jaehong’s heavy breathing]
Ah, why don't you calm down?
[Leo] If you follow the hallway
There is an exit
That's where our kids will come.
take it
It's your father's
[Meaningful music]
[Ding! - Elevator]
Hey, who is this?
huh? Take your elevator
Where are you going?
I have to get on that, get off, quickly.
- [Beep]
- Get down, quickly!
Can't you understand me?
Come here!
[Sad music]
[Hocheol] Daughter, is there anything you want?
Nadika
Digital camera?
Videos work too
"Loading"
[Bang! -Camera]
[Nervous music]
[Mansik] Where are you? Mr.
[Wham - Siren]
Huh? Team leader, here
Okay
Oh, team leader, be careful with the car, car.
- [Mansik] Oh, oh!
- [조직원] 내려 봐!
Hey, fuck it!
- Come out, come out, Mr.
- [Organization member] Park!
Fuck it quickly
Uh, team leader, car, car, car, car
Oh, hey, hold on tight!
꽉 잡아, 잡았구나, 아!
- Ah, ah, ah!
- [Dongju] Huh?
I have nowhere to go
No Pakkuda
Come out, come out, come out, come out!
- [Mansik] What is this?
- [Dongju] Oh!
[만식] 이것들이 미쳤나, 씨
[Mansik’s rough breathing]
Let's go up
[Male/Russian]
위에 올라가서 돈 챙겨 가자
Yoon Dong...
- [덕규] 아, 누구라고?
- [웅얼대며] 윤동주
Who?
- [Pan Yeol mutters]
- Yes?
[Panel heat] Yun...
[Deokgyu] Ah, Mr.
Anyway, take care of yourself, okay?
Go, go, go
[Wing - Cell Phone]
[Panel heat] Ah...
[Guide voice] For now...
[Wudangtang]
[Wham - Siren]
[Jooyoung’s heavy breathing]
It's noisy, Mr.
[crunch]
Hey
can you do it?
If you start a fight, you have to finish it.
- See you later.
- [Mansik] Huh?
I didn't tell you to go alone
[Dongju/Narration]
The moment you step into the ring
[Emotional music]
There is no place to retreat
If you've started
You have to risk everything
Dongju! It's all here!
here! Dong...
[The spirit of the organization members]
[Dongju/Narration]
Move forward with all your might
[Judge/English] 30 seconds ago
[English] Preparation
[English] Start
[Dongju/Narration] End the silence
It's time to explode
"Justice"
[Noisy]
[Leo] Take it, it's your father's
Minjooyoung!
[Seokchun] But did you come alone?
[Jonghyun] So easily
'Cause I'm not the one to die
[Seokchun] You stupid bastard!
[Dongju] Hannah
Hannah, come to your senses, Jihanna!
[Seokchun] Shut up!
Niga*
Because the truck was sent off late,
[Hannah] That’s why I came here
Minjooyoung heard from someone.
[Jonghyun] Minjooyoung
I won't give up candy
- [Man's scream]
- [Dongju] I’m just curious.
Since when did you hate me so much?
- From the beginning
-Why?
[Jonghyun] I hated smiling
[Dongju/Narration] Torn and broken
Even if my body breaks
Until you crush your opponent
The king
I will never die
[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]